We build websites, we're at 20 million bucks in revenue.
We're in an industry where AI is very disruptive.
You know, AI is making it easier and easier
for our customers to be able to build their own websites.
You have a story around AI is decaying the business,
but all I hear is that your job just got way easier.
Explain.
I think there's plenty of people
who will just be super laggards on this
and are not gonna be replet vibe coding.
They never bought your to begin with.
Like the person who is super into AI right now
wasn't hiring WAS anyways, they built their own website.
How cashflow positive are you right now?
3.6 in EBITDA last year.
That's lowish.
We're heavy on people.
Dude, AI.
Have you heard?
Big thing.
It's like you're worried about them doing it,
you're not even doing it.
I would probably spend the next six months
reorganizing the workflow,
probably reduce headcount by 50%,
using AI workflows in order to actually do the same thing,
increase the margin from 3.6 to like seven.
That's how I'd actually fix it.